Guide to the CONSOL Energy, Inc. Mine Maps and Records, 1857-2010 AIS.1991.16
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Survey Books, 1880s-1990s; XVI.
  - Miscellaneous Survey Books, 6.
    - Miscellaneous Notes No. 1322; Division No. 1; Drill hole locations, Property surveys; Verner Mine, Cherry Valley Mine, Brier Hill Mine; Miscellaneous Notes No. 1484; Division No. 1; Property surveys, Road locations; Harrison Mine, Champion Mine, Bridgeville Mine, Partridge Mine (Box 111, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous Notes No. 1579, outside; Division No. 1; Country Pits; Moon Run Mine, Bell Mine, Margerum Mine, Partridge Mine, Essen Mine # 3, Cherry Mine, Federal Mine; Miscellaneous Notes No. 419; Division No. 3; Tunnel notes; Bell Mine, Moon Run Mine, Chartiers Mine (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Notes No. 295; Division No. 6; Topographical lines; Banner Mine, Courtney Mine; Railroad locations; Miscellaneous Notes No. 296; Division No. 6; Banner Mine, Eleanora Mine, Little Squaw Mine, Grindstone Mine (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Notes No. 889; Division No. 7; House and road locations, Property surveys; Tremont Mine, Somers Mine # 2 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Notes No. 666; Division No. 8; Property lines, Building locations, Gas wells, Topography; Miscellaneous Notes No. 292; Division No. 9; Land levels, Property lines and levels (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Notes No. 1385; Division No. 9; Property notes; Banning Mine # 1 & 2, West Newton Mine; Miscellaneous Notes No. 320, Construction; Division No. 10; Railroad location, Masonry levels and foundations (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Notes No. 417, outside; Division No. 10; Banning Mine # 1, Darr Mine, Wick Haven Mine; Railroad levels; Miscellaneous Notes No. 1439; Division No. 11; Property surveys; Walton Mine # 2, Coal Bluff Mine, Wolfe Mine (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Notes No. 887; Division No. 12; Gallatin Mine, Sunnyside Mine, Pittsburgh & Lake Erie Railroad, Mongah Mine; Gas well locations; Coal Bluff Mine, Bunola Mine (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Notes No. 930; Division No. 12; Gallatin Mine, Warden Mine, West Newton Mine, Ocean Mine, Forest Hill Mine, Euclid Mine, Coal Bluff Mine, Pittsburgh & Lake Erie Railroad (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Notes No. 4062, outside; Division No. 12; Road and building locations, Creek levels, Property surveys; Mongah Mine, Star Mine; Miscellaneous Notes No. 888; Division No. 13; Crescent Mine, Vigilant Mine, Eclipse Mine; Land elevations, Road locations, Property surveys (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Notes No. 888; Division No. 13; Crescent Mine, Vigilant Mine, Eclipse Mine; Land elevations, Road locations, Property surveys; New work scheduled to be done on mines (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Time book no. 494 ½, 1919; Montour Mine # 10; Library Shops, Time Book (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - Unidentified Mine # 359; Weekly Time Book (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - Wells, Wells drilled on farm tracts (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - Wells, oil and gas, Wells, oil and gas to be located (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Outside Notes, 7.
    This subseries includes information on outside notes from the mines. Mine engineers would use these books to record a multitude of annotations, such as road levels, creek locations and land elevations. The books can include information on mines, railroads, and topography. The books are further organized by issuing Division.
    - Outside extension notes, No. 1; Outside notes No. 1, levels (Box 112, Folder 15)
    - Outside notes No. 65, 66; Bradley Mine; Farm locations, Property locations; Outside surveys No. 168; Railroad levels, Property lines, Pit surveys (Box 112, Folder 16)
    - Outside surveys No. 203; Farm surveys and topography; Ocean Mine, West Newton Mine; Outside notes No. 234; Pit measurements, Topography levels, Road levels; Banning Mine # 2 (Box 112, Folder 17)
    - Outside notes No. 247; Property locations, Connecting mines; Shaw Mine; Outside notes No. 278; Property lines and levels, Railroad surveys; Banning Mine # 2 (Box 112, Folder 18)
    - Outside surveys No. 361; Survey connecting J.L. Kirk Coal to Glenshaw Mine; Mifflin Mine # 2; Outside surveys No. 363; Topographical survey, Bridge changes; Montour Railroad, Shaw Mine (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Outside surveys No. 413; Property levels, Railroad lines; Partridge Mine, Ridgeway-Bishop Mine, Banning Mine No. 1; Outside surveys No. 423; Property line surveys; Beechmont Mine, Keeling Mine (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Outside notes No. 428; Topographical survey, Railroad levels; Outside notes No. 474; Coal boat and coal barge measurements, 1905 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Outside notes No. 478; Property survey; Location of Redstone Creek; Smock Mine; Outside notes No. 489; Loose-leaf binder, blueprints (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Outside notes No. 491; Essen Mine, Margerum Mine, Moon Run Mine, First Hill Mine, Partridge Mine; Outside surveys No. 491, vicinity mines; Survey between properties and mines (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Outside levels No. 501; Outside notes No. 505; Darr Mine; Crop lines, Topographical surveys (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Outside surveys No. 507; Anderson Mine, Nottingham Mine, First Pool Mine; Elevation levels; Outside surveys No. 508; Banner Mine; Topographical and railroad survey (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Outside surveys No. 511; To connect Donaldson Line to Winstein Survey; Outside surveys No. 513; Berry Farm Survey (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Outside Survey Lines No. 513; Allison Mine, Boon Mine, Vulcan Mine; Baltimore & Ohio Railroad extension; Western Washington Railroad survey; Outside notes No. 515; Wabash Railroad survey; Topographical survey; Slope Mine (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Outside notes No. 516; Baltimore & Ohio Railroad, Port Royal Mine, Waverly Mine; Outside Lines No. 517; Property tracts; Snowden Mine (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Outside notes No. 521; Banning Mine; Whitsett Mine topography; Railroad surveys; Outside notes No. 529; Wabash Railroad; Buildings location, Land tract surveys; Vulcan Mine; Survey to connect Vulcan Mine and Morgan Mine with Essen Mine properties (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Outside notes No. 534; Line connections, Public roads, Colonial ovens; Outside notes No. 536 (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Outside levels No. 537 (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - Outside surveys No. 539; Meadowlands; Railroad survey; Outside levels No. 540 (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - Outside surveys No. 541; Outside surveys No. 542; Baltimore & Ohio Railroad (Box 113, Folder 15)
    - Outside notes No. 546; Property survey, Railroad notes; Outside notes No. 546; Land tract surveys (Box 113, Folder 16)
    - Outside levels No. 547; Outside survey No. 552; Pipeline, Farm and land tracts (Box 113, Folder 17)
    - Outside notes No. 586; Midland Mine # 3; Land tract surveys; Wabash Railroad location; Outside notes No. 587; Topography, Railroads; First Pool Mine # 1, Lick Run Mine (Box 113, Folder 18)
    - Outside notes No. 591; Colonial Mine, Little Squaw Mine, Grindstone Mine; Outside notes No. 591; Creedmoor Mine, National Mine, Laurel Hill Mine # 2, Vulcan Mine (Box 113, Folder 19)
    - Outside notes No. 595; Property surveys; Laurel Hill Mine # 2, Creedmoor Mine; Outside notes No. 597; Banning Mine, Eureka Mine, Darr Mine, Whitsett Mine (Box 113, Folder 20)
    - Outside notes No. 597; Banning Mine, Eureka Mine, Darr Mine, Whitsett Mine; Outside notes No. 598; Anderson Mine, First Pool Mine, Gastonville Mine, Fairhaven Mine (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Outside notes No. 598; Anderson Mine, Fairhaven Mine, First Pool Mine; Wiers Run; Outside notes No. 600; Grindstone Mine (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Outside notes No. 605; Eclipse Mine, Lick Run Mine, First Pool Mine; Outside notes No. 610; Arnold Mine, Equitable Mine, Manown Mine, Somers Mine # 2 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Outside levels No. 612; Railroad levels; Colonial Mine # 1; Outside notes No. 623; Rowes Run; Park Hill Mine; Pittsburgh, Virginia & Charleston Railroad line levels (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Outside notes No. 623; Pittsburgh, Virginia & Charleston Railroad; Rowes Run, Grindstone, Park Hill; Outside notes No. 630; Line topography; Banner Mine, Colonial Mine # 1; Rowes Run (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Outside notes No. 634; Property surveys, Levels; Waynesburg Coal; Outside notes No. 639; Property lines surveys, Topography notes (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Outside notes No. 640; Land tract surveys; Western Washington Railroad survey; Outside notes No. 644; Topography, Washwater Run; Property surveys; Little Squaw Mine (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Outside notes No. 649; Creek survey; Somers Mine # 2, Manown Mine, Arnold Mine; Outside notes No. 651; Forest Hill Shaft, Ocean Mine # 2 shaft; Road and gas well locations, Property survey levels (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Outside notes No. 661; Property lines and levels, Plot lines; First Pool Mine; Outside notes No. 663; Farm surveys, Property contours; Ocean Mine # 2 Surface, Yough Slope Mine (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Outside notes No. 665; Property surveys and levels, Oil wells, Road locations; Outside notes No. 667; Creek locations, Property surveys; Equitable Mine, Arnold Mine # 2, Somers Mine # 2; Building locations (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Outside notes No. 669; Property surveys, Building locations; Essen Mine # 3, Vulcan Mine; Farm properties, oil wells; Outside levels No. 669; Gas well locations, Property surveys, Farm property notes; Harrison Mine, Federal Mine # 2, Essen Mine # 3, Morgan Mine, Northwestern Mine (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Outside notes No. 672; Waverly Mine, Cedar Creek; Property surveys; Naomi Coal, Banning Mine; Outside notes No. 674; Coal Bluff Mine, Walton Mine, Hilldale Mine; Philadelphia Gas Co. (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Outside notes No. 674; Coal Bluff Mine, Walton Mine # 2; Philadelphia Gas Co.; Pittsburgh, Virginia & Charleston Railroad; Outside notes No. 679; Land tract surveys; Becks Run Railroad; Walton Mine # 1, Pool Mine (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Outside notes No. 679; Frank Hill; Railroad notes; Outside notes No. 746; Equitable Mine, Gallatin Mine; Property lines and levels (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - Outside notes No. 763; Pit locations, Property surveys; Wick Haven Mine, Banning Mine # 3, Harwat Mine, Eureka Mine, Port Royal Mine; Outside notes No. 764; Property lines, levels and elevations, Measurements (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - Outside notes No. 764; Property lines, levels and elevations, Measurements; Outside notes No. 765; Property surveys and connections, Railroad lines (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - Outside notes No. 767; Property lines and surveys, Pit locations; West Newton Mine, Bigley Mine, Gaffey Mine, Ocean Mine # 5 (Box 114, Folder 17)
    - Outside notes No. 768; Land surveys, Heir tracts; Chartiers Southern Railroad; Land connection surveys, Property surveys; Montour Mine # 1; Outside notes No. 770; Waynesburg and Washington Railroad location; Dickson Mine, Moon Run Mine (Box 114, Folder 18)
    - Outside notes No. 770; Property surveys; Waynesburg and Washington Railroad location; Dickson Mine, Moon Run Mine; Outside notes No. 774; Farmland surveys, Property surveys; Chartiers Southern Railroad; Waynesburg and Washington Railroad (Box 114, Folder 19)
    - Outside notes No. 774; Farmland surveys, Property surveys; Chartiers Southern Railroad; Waynesburg and Washington Railroad; Outside notes No. 776; Property surveys, lines and levels, Railroad location; Nottingham Mine, Montour Mine # 10, First Pool Mine # 2 (Box 114, Folder 20)
    - Outside notes No. 776; Property surveys, lines and levels, Railroad location; Nottingham Mine, Montour Mine # 10, First Pool Mine # 2; Outside notes No. 777; Camden Mine, Risher Mine, Hilldale Mine, Yough Mine; No. 2, Coal Bluff Mine; Transit notes, Pit locations, Property surveys (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Outside notes No. 777; Camden Mine, Risher Mine, Hilldale Mine, Yough Mine; No. 2, Coal Bluff Mine; Transit notes, Pit locations, Property surveys; Outside notes No. 778; Property levels, Gas well locations; Montour Mine # 8, # 10, Nottingham Mine, Cincinnati Mine (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Outside notes No. 783; Topography, Gas well locations, Property levels and contours; Montour Railroad; Lick Run Mine, Montour Mine # 10 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Outside notes No. 784; Margerum Mine, Dickson Mine, Independent Mine; Oil well location; Montour Railroad (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Outside notes No. 787; Gas well locations; Cincinnati Mine, First Pool Mine # 2, Montour Mine # 8, Nottingham Mine; Triangulation: Happer, Darragh, Phillips; Transit lines; Montour Railroad (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Outside notes No. 792; Montour Railroad; Railroad connections, Building locations, Topography; Triangulation: Harger, Anderson, Finley, Fife, Pollack, Thomas; Outside notes No. 794; Railroad bridges, Pier locations, Property levels and lines, Drawings (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Outside notes No. 795 (continued in 802); Fence locations, House relocations; Pittsburgh, Virginia & Charleston Railroad survey; Property surveys, levels and lines; Black Diamond Mine, Catsburg Mine (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Outside notes No. 800; Property surveys, Pit locations, Outside levels, Farm locations; Waverly Hollow; Outside notes No. 800; Property surveys, Shore locations; Pittsburgh & Lake Erie Railroad; Eureka Mine # 4, Banning Mine # 3, Waverly Mine (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Outside notes No. 803; Property notes, lines and levels, Creek and spring locations, Power line locations; Catsburg Mine, Black Diamond Mine (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Outside notes No. 805; Pittsburgh, Virginia & Charleston Railroad; Property surveys, Gas well locations; Cincinnati Mine, Old Buffalo Mine, Courtney Mine, Coal Bluff Mine; Outside notes No. 807; Property surveys, lines and levels, Gas well locations; Piney Fork Mine, Montour Mine # 10; Montour Railroad (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Outside notes No. 807; Property surveys, lines and levels, Gas well locations; Piney Fork Mine, Montour Mine # 10; Montour Railroad; Outside notes No. 808; Gas well locations; Montour Mine # 8, Cincinnati Mine, Nottingham Mine, Eclipse Mine (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Outside notes No. 811; Gas line locations, Pipeline locations; Partridge Mine, Moon Run Mine, Summer Hill Mine; Property surveys, lines and levels (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Outside notes No. 812; Property surveys, lines and levels, Building locations; Country Mine, Somers Mine, Arnold Mine # 1 (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - Outside notes No. 813; Property surveys, Building and road locations; Pittsburgh & Lake Erie Railroad; Eureka Mine, Waverly Mine, Euclid Mine; Outside notes No. 815; Property surveys, lines and levels, Farm survey; Montour Mine # 10, Lick Run Mine (Box 115, Folder 14)
    - Outside notes No. 815; Property surveys, lines and levels, Farm survey; Montour Mine # 10, Lick Run Mine; Outside notes No. 816; Road levels, Property surveys, Gas well locations, Land connections (Box 115, Folder 15)
    - Outside notes No. 816; Road levels, Property surveys, Gas well locations, Land connections; Outside notes No. 818; Montour Mine # 10, Presto Mine; Property surveys and elevations; Location of things needed for Coal Co. (Box 115, Folder 16)
    - Outside notes No. 818; Montour Mine # 10, Presto Mine; Property surveys and elevations; Location of things needed for Coal Co.; Outside notes No. 821; Property surveys, lines and levels, Farmland notes; Redstone Vein Mine, Yough Slope Mine, West Newton Mine, Ocean Mine # 2, # 5 (Box 115, Folder 17)
    - Outside notes No. 821; Property surveys, lines and levels, Farmland notes; Redstone Vein Mine, Yough Slope Mine, West Newton Mine, Ocean Mine # 2, # 5; Outside notes No. 823; Gas well locations; Harrison Mine, Panhandle Mine, Mansfield Mine, Bridgeville Mine, Summer Hill Mine (Box 115, Folder 18)
    - Outside notes No. 823; Gas well locations; Harrison Mine, Panhandle Mine, Mansfield Mine, Bridgeville Mine, Summer Hill Mine; Outside notes No. 825; Property surveys, Shaft measurements, Land connections; Equitable Mine, Ocean Mine # 5, Guiler Mine (Box 115, Folder 19)
    - Outside notes No. 826; Property surveys and connections, Property lines; Coal Bluff Mine; Pittsburgh, Virginia & Charleston Railroad tracks; Outside notes No. 828; Montour Mine # 8, # 10, Experimental Mine, First Pool Mine, Lick Run Mine; Property surveys, topography, lines and elevations (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Outside notes No. 829; Property surveys, lines and levels, Creek and building locations; Somers Mine, Arnold Mine # 2; Outside notes No. 830; Property surveys, elevations, Oil well location; Moon Run Mine, Partridge Mine, Margerum Mine, Dickson Mine (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Outside notes No. 831; Property surveys, Road locations, Creek locations (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Outside notes No. 834; Banning Mine # 1, Black Diamond Mine, Eureka Mine, Arnold Mine; Road locations, Property surveys, Water well locations; Outside notes No. 835; Crescent Mine Surface, Albany Mine, Eclipse Mine, Champion Mine; Gas well locations, Road locations, Property surveys (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Outside notes No. 835; Crescent Mine Surface, Albany Mine, Eclipse Mine, Champion Mine; Gas well locations, Road locations, Property surveys; Outside notes No. 840; Property surveys, Gas well locations; Midland Mine # 1, # 3, Allison Mine; Chartiers Valley Railroad (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Outside notes No. 840; Property surveys, Gas well locations; Midland Mine # 1, # 3, Allison Mine; Chartiers Valley Railroad; Outside notes No. 841; Property surveys, Creek locations, Gas well locations; Fayette City; Somers Mine # 2, Arnold Mine, Banning Mine (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Outside notes No. 841; Property surveys, Creek locations, Gas well locations; Fayette City; Somers Mine # 2, Arnold Mine, Banning Mine; Outside notes No. 843; Property lines and levels; Pittsburgh & Lake Erie Railroad; Arnold Mine # 2, Banning Mine # 1, # 2, # 3, Eureka Mine (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Outside notes No. 844; Cincinnati Mine; Property surveys, elevations, lines and levels; Building locations; Outside notes No. 845; Property lines, Gas well locations; Ocean Mine # 1, # 2, # 5, West Newton Mine, Forest Hill Mine; Pittsburgh & Lake Erie Railroad (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - Outside notes No. 848; Dickson Mine, Moon Run Mine; Montour Junction; Property lines and levels, Gas well locations; Outside notes No. 849; Property surveys, lines and levels, Gas well locations; Manown Mine, Gallatin Mine, Sunnyside Mine (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Outside notes No. 849; Property surveys, lines and levels, Gas well locations; Manown Mine, Gallatin Mine, Sunnyside Mine; Outside notes No. 854; Chartiers Gas Coal Co.; Gas well locations, Property surveys; Midland Mine # 1, # 3 (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - Outside notes No. 854; Chartiers Gas Coal Co.; Gas well locations, Property surveys; Midland Mine # 1, # 3; Outside notes No. 856; Euclid Mine, Yough Slope Mine, West Newton Mine, Banning Mine # 2; Gas well locations, Property surveys, lines and levels (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - Outside notes No. 864; Property surveys, lines and levels, Road locations; Wheeling & Lake Erie Railroad; Adena Mine, Robyville Mine; Outside notes No. 871; Ocean Mine # 2, Warden Mine; Douglas Hollow; Property surveys, lines and levels, Drain location proposal (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - Outside notes No. 873; Property survey and elevations, Proposed drain locations; Warden Mine, Ocean Mine # 2, Lovedale Mine; Douglas Hollow; Outside notes No. 874; Property surveys, Power line locations; Ocean Mine # 2, Forest Hill Mine, Warden Mine (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - Outside notes No. 879; Property surveys, Sales, House locations; West Newton Mine, Shaner Mine, Warden Mine, Ocean Mine # 2, # 5; Outside notes No. 899; Road improvements, Line levels; Midland Mine # 1, Montour Mine # 4, Essen Mine # 3, Jumbo Mine, Partridge Mine (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - Outside notes No. 899; Road improvements, Line levels; Midland Mine # 1, Montour Mine # 4, Essen Mine # 3, Jumbo Mine, Partridge Mine; Outside notes No. 908; Ocean Mine # 2, Banning Mine # 2, Eureka Mine, Warden Mine; Property surveys, Road and slate dump locations, Power lines (Box 116, Folder 15)
    - Outside notes No. 920; Warden Mine, Banning Mine, Ocean Mine, Euclid Mine (Box 116, Folder 16)
    - Outside general construction notes No. 934; Banning Mine, Ocean Mine, Warden Mine (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Outside notes No. 935; Division No. 13; Gas well locations (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Outside general construction notes No. 938; Banning Mine, Crescent Mine, Montour Mine # 10, Ocean Mine, Warden Mine (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Outside general construction notes; Contour levels (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Outside notes No. 1041; Property surveys, Oil well location, Telephone pole location; Jumbo Mine, Nickel Plate Mine, Willow Grove Mine, Vulcan Mine, Champion Mine; Outside notes No. 1074; Property surveys; Buffalo Mine, Imperial Mine, Mingo Creek Mine (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Outside notes No. 1100; Outside notes No. 1148; Oil and gas locations, Property surveys; Brier Hill Mine, Jumbo Mine, Bishop Mine, Montour Mine (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Outside levels No. 1149; Outside notes No. 1281; Midland Mine; Property surveys, Gas well locations, Building and road locations (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Outside notes No. 1389; Property surveys; Henderson Mine, O.I.C. Mine, Bridgeville Mine, Essen Mine; No. 2; Outside notes No. 1502; Hough Mine, Echo Mine, Arnold Mine, Little Redstone Mine (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Outside notes No. 1669; Property surveys; Laurel Hill Mine # 1, Willow Grove Mine, Montour Mine # 9, Moon Run Mine, Strip Mine; Outside notes No. 1719; Property levels (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Outside notes No. 4020; Montour Mine # 10, Eclipse Mine; Montour Railroad; Outside notes No. 4046; Partridge Mine, Moon Run Mine, Bridgeville Mine, Montour Mine # 9, Essen Mine # 3 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Outside notes No. 4046; Partridge Mine, Moon Run Mine, Bridgeville Mine, Montour Mine # 9, Essen Mine # 3; Outside notes No. 4049; Property surveys; Somers Mine, Crescent Mine (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Outside notes No. 4051; Bore hole locations; Ocean Mine, Wick Haven Mine, Ruth Mine, Warden Mine, Eureka Mine, Banning Mine # 1, Port Royal Mine; Outside notes No. 4058; Eastern Ohio Field (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Outside notes No. 4061; Arnold Mine, Allison Mine, Lindley Mine; Property levels, Road and building locations; Hazel Mine (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Outside notes No. 4063; Panhandle Division, Canonsburg Section; Westland Mine, Midland Mine, Lindley Mine; Property surveys and levels, Road and building location, Railroads; Outside notes No. 4067; River Division (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - Outside notes No. 4073; Panhandle Division; Property surveys and levels, Base line survey, River levels (Box 117, Folder 15)
    - Outside notes No. 4075; Property surveys, Oil well location, Building location; Midland Mine, Westland Mine (Box 117, Folder 16)
    - Outside notes No. 4076; Panhandle Division; Montour Mine # 9, Harrison Mine, Midland Mine, Davis Mine (Box 117, Folder 17)
    - Outside notes No. 4077; Panhandle Division; Proposed lot locations, Property surveys and levels, Building locations; Montour Mine # 4, 8 (Box 117, Folder 18)
    - Outside notes No. 4078; Panhandle Division; Property levels, Road and building locations; Westland Mine, Midland Mine, Lindley Mine, Montour Mine # 4 (Box 117, Folder 19)
    - Outside notes No. 4079; River division; Warden Mine, Euclid Mine, Ocean Mine # 1, Banning Mine # 1; Topography, Bore hole locations, Property levels (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Outside notes No. 4081; Panhandle Division, Library Corps; Montour Mine # 4, # 10; Outside notes No. 4081; Montour Mine # 4, # 10; Property surveys and levels, Road locations (Box 118, Folder 2)